

ESAD BORAN

Computer Engineer esadboran.github.io

PROFILE

I am a recent graduate in Computer Engineering from Hacettepe University. I have experience in backend development using C# ASP.NET and Java Spring. Additionally, I have conducted research and developed projects in Machine Learning and Deep Learning with Python. I am currently pursuing a career as a full stack developer.

CONTACT



+90 553 463 91 19



esatsuphi@gmail.com



linkedin/esadboran



github/esadboran

LANGUAGE

• English (B2 Level)

CERTIFICATE

TensorFlow Developer Certificate

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and **Optimization**

INTRODUCTION TO TENSORFLOW FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE, MACHINE LEARNING, AND DEEP

Türk Telekom & TRAI Veri Bilimi Analitiği

(40+ HOURS) PYTHON | ADVANCED PROGRAMMING FROM ZERO

EDUCATION

HACETTEPE UNIVERSITY (2018 - 2024)

• GPA: 3.22 / 4

SUPHİ KOYUNCUOĞLU ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL (2014 - 2018)

• GPA: 89.27 / 100

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EXPERIENCE

TÜRKİYE PETROLLERİ A.O. (TPAO) | October 2023 – June 2024

- Developed a modern, user-friendly and high-performance 3D Data Visualization Engine capable of visualizing seismic, well and surface data used in the petroleum sector.
- Created a new module for the TPAO Applications Platform to manage, receive and track requests made from within the company to the R&D center.
- Developed modules for the Digital TPAO project that enable users to upload and visualize the Surface data.
- Skills Used: ThreeJS, .NET, C#, Frontend (UI), Git

GELİR İDARESİ BAŞKANLIĞI | June 2023 - July 2023

INTERN

- Developed a module with Spring that allows users to view their bills, make payments and calculate taxes.
- Gained the opportunity to learn and apply technologies such as Spring and MySQL.
- · Skills Used: Spring, Java, Frontend (UI), Git

SiSBiM | June 2022 - July 2022

INTFRN

- · Developed cloned Django projects resembling Netflix, Blog and Instagram using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Skills Used: Django, Frontend (UI)

ODAKGIS | October 2018 - November 2018 INTERN

PROJECT

- Graduation Project: Active Object Tracking on a Drone with Airsim
- Website: esadboran.github.io/BitirmeProjesi
- Developed a car lane tracking detection system.
- Created panoramic images using multiple images.
- Implemented object detection using deep neural networks with artificial intelligence.

SKILL

- Programming Languages: C#, Python, Java, C++, SQL, C
- · Backend Technologies: .NET, Spring
- Artificial Intelligence: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Computer Vision
- Web: React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Data Analysis, Data Structures, Algorithms, LaTeX, Git
- · Word, Excel, Powerpoint

REFERENCE

Software Engineer Manager Muhsin Gürel TÜRKİYE PETROLLERİ A.O.

